Well, good afternoon and welcome to the
August 3rd meeting of the Public
Services Committee.
Um,
we have two items on our agenda today.
If you are here with us in um, chambers,
if you would make sure that you silence
your cell phone,
and when you approach the podium to
speak, if you would make sure that the
green light is on and the two, um,
also state your name, um, for the
record, please.
If you are joining us virtually and
would like to make a comment, please use
the virtual hand, um, and raise that and
it when Jennifer acknowledges you,
you'll be able to speak. We are going to
be using a 3-minute timer today for
public comment.
So, with that, um, if you would read the
first item, Jennifer.
>> Please. Number six, ordinance third
reading annexing to the city of
Cheyenne, Wyoming, land west of Roundtop
Road and south of Happy Jack Road.
>> Thank you. And staff report, please.
>> Uh, Madam Chair, members of the
committee, Connor White, Planning and
Development Department. Uh, just as a
reminder with this annexation, it is on
third reading. Uh, this is south of
Happy Jack, so it has nothing to do with
the Cox annexation.
That's postponed till September. It does
not touch that property whatsoever.
It's adjacent to North Range Business
Park.
So, it is contiguous. It already has
outside user
agreement for water that was approved by
this governing body.
And
it has a county approved site plan.
For a basically storage laydown
construction yard.
I have no further information. There's
been no additional public comment.
There's been no phone calls to our
department on this annexation. So, I'm
available for any questions.
>> Thank you. Any questions for staff?
Dr. Rinne?
Okay. We'll go out for public comment.
Is there any public comment?
Mr. Emmons?
>> I'm Adam Chair, Brad Emmons, AVI agent
for the applicant and owner. And we also
have Microsoft with Rachel Ewing online.
So, be here to answer any questions that
the committee has.
>> Thank you.
Any other public comment?
Hearing none or seeing none, we will
I would entertain a motion.
>> Madam Chairwoman, I would move to
approve on third reading.
>> Second.
>> We have a motion to approve and a
second.
Is there any discussion?
Okay, hearing none, all in favor say I.
>> I.
>> Opposed?
This item will move forward with the
recommendation to approve at the next
meeting of the council. Next item,
please.
>> Number seven, ordinance third reading
amending the official zoning map of the
city of Cheyenne establishing the zoning
classification of BP Business Park for
land annexed to the city of Cheyenne
located west of Round Top Road and south
of Happy Jack Road.
>> Okay, staff report, please.
>> Madam Chair, members of the committee,
Connor Wei, Planning and Development
Department.
So, with any annexation, there's the
assigned zoning.
We look at surrounding zoning within the
city as well as the current use of the
property and that's how we determine
uh, what staff recommends for the
assigned zoning. Uh, with this property
as I mentioned has approval from the
county for basically construction yard,
so industrial style use. It is adjacent
to North Orange Business Park which is
all for the most part zone,
uh, BP Business Park.
Um, so it has Business Park on two
sides. So that's why staff recommended
Business Park for this property.
I have no further information. We have
had no public additional public comment
on this. I am available for any
questions.
>> Thank you. Is there any question for
staff?
Okay, public comment.
Any public comment?
Hearing none or seeing none,
I would entertain a motion.
>> Madam Chairwoman, I move to approve on
third and final reading.
>> Second.
>> We have a motion by Dr. Emmons and a
second by Dr. Rennie.
Um,
all in favor say I.
>> I.
>> Opposed?
This item will be, um, moved to the
council with a recommendation to
approve, um, at the next meeting of the
governing body. Uh, with that we
finished everything on our agenda today,
um,
and I think we're like in 4 minutes. So
way to go, guys. It is a record. Um,
have a great day and see you next week.
Tina, did you shut off the Zoom?